http://www.peterborough-diocese.org.uk/main/privacy-policy

We use cookies to improve your experience of our site.
By continuing to browse the site you are agreeing to our use of cookies. ContinueFind out more
Menu
HomeNews & eventsPublicationsContact usLog in
The Church of England in Northamptonshire, Peterborough and Rutland
WelcomeChurch schoolsDiocesan informationMission and ministry
Data Protection and Privacy – The Diocese of Peterborough
The Peterborough Diocesan Board of Finance (PDBF) commits to complying with the Data Protection Act 2018 and takes the privacy of personal data very seriously.
Like any organisation, the PDBF needs to process personal data in order to fulfil its legitimate purposes, principally the furtherance of the mission and ministry of the Anglican Church in Peterborough, Rutland and Northamptonshire. Each organisation is to have a document, known as a Privacy Notice E-Bulletin; the purpose of which is to explain to people how and why their data is being processed. Our General Privacy Notice can be downloaded from the link further down the page. This privacy notice explains the processing of personal data for clergy, licensed and authorised lay ministers, parish officers and other parish role holders, school contacts and other key contacts, and therefore covers the majority of processing of personal data.
The PDBF is a broad and diverse organisation, and therefore there are some areas of our work which have dedicated privacy notices in order to better explain the processing of personal data in each context. These can also be downloaded by clicking on the links below. These notices are being kept under regular review and the most recent versions will be uploaded to this webpage, so please do check this webpage periodically.
PDBF General Privacy Policy
PDBF Privacy Notice for E-Bulletin (Mailings)
PDBF Website Privacy Policy
PDBF Discernment Privacy Policy
Who should I contact if I have a question?
Our aim is to be as open and transparent about our data processing as possible. If you have any queries or concerns about the processing of your personal data, please contact our Data Protection Officer, Susan Ratcliffe, through one of the routes below:
Post: The Diocesan Office, The Palace, Peterborough, PE1 1BA
Email: sue.ratcliffe@peterborough-diocese.org.uk
Telephone: 01733 887039
Should you wish to contact the Information Commissioner’s Office, they can be contacted through the following routes:
Post: Information Commissioner’s Office, Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF
Email: https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/email
Telephone: 0303 123 1133
For more information about the processing of your data, please contact Susan Ratcliffe (as shown above).
If you spot any information or personal data which is incorrect or out-of-date on the Diocesan website, please contact communications@peterborough-diocese.org.uk.
Find us on:
© Diocese of Peterborough. All rights reserved.
|  Privacy Policy
|  Photo Credits
The Peterborough Diocesan Board of Finance. A Company limited by guarantee, registered in London No. 186179
Registered address: The Palace, Peterborough PE1 1YB. Registered Charity No. 250569. VAT No. 737
926
395
The Peterborough Diocesan Board of Education has charitable status as part of the DBF, linked by a uniting direction under 596(5) of the Charities Act 1993
Website and CMS by Adept
WelcomeChurch schoolsDiocesan informationMission and ministry
HomeNews & eventsPublicationsContact usLog in
